kazeli.com 2015-12-29

# Kazeli Web Office: Simple CRM, Website Design and Builder, Online File Storage, Business Network, Automatic Follow Up, Cloud Computing - Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy**

Kazeli Holdings Ltd. is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. By visiting www.kazeli.com you are accepting this Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before you use www.kazeli.com. This privacy policy only applies to: www.kazeli.com and not to websites controlled by other companies or organisations we may link to.

**Who Controls my Information?**

Any information provided to or gathered from www.kazeli.com is controlled by Kazeli Holding Ltd., headquartered at: 2 Agias Elenis str., 6th floor, Stassinos Building, 1060 Nicosia - Cyprus. Tel: +357 22 879865 Fax: +357 22 517397.

**What do I agree to by using this website?**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use by www.kazeli.com of any information you provide. From time to time, we reserve the right to up-date and change our privacy policy, however our privacy policy on this page will always be up-dated and current with so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Do you disclose my information to third parties?**

www.kazeli.com may provide statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.  
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. These functions include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and emails, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer services. These companies and individuals will have access to the personal information they need to perform these functions, but they may not use it for any other purposes.

www.kazeli.com may work with other companies to provide offers and promotions that may be of interest to you. You will only receive notification of these offers if you have indicated your willingness to be contacted for such purposes and we will only provide your contact details to third parties for marketing purposes if you have given us permission to do so. www.kazeli.com will not sell or loan your data to third parties nor will any of the third parties be allowed access to your data.

**What information do you collect and how is it used?**

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at www.kazeli.com.

  * **Registration Information**  
In order to provide you with the most fast, efficient and accurate service possible, kazeli.com requires the collection of certain personally identifiable information. The information that may be collected includes: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.  

  * **Email Information**  
In an effort to optimize our email communication with you we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from www.kazeli.com if your computer supports such capabilities. You may of course use the unsubscribe link found on the bottom of such email communications from us to remove your name from our mailing list.  

  * **Cookies**  
When you visit one www.kazeli.com, we may also store some information on your computer's hard drive in the form of a "Cookie". Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. We may use cookies to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our Site. To do so, the cookies we use may record identifiable information pertaining to your preferences for viewing particular web pages. We may also use cookies to collect identifiable information to help us in analyzing trends, tracking user's movement, and gathering broad demographic information for aggregate use.

You can however control the use of cookies on your computer. You can adjust your browser to: prevent it from accepting new cookies, to be notified you when you receive a new cookie or you may even disable cookies altogether. However,  the use of cookies will ensure a more personalized and innovative Kazeli website experience.

We use the information to handle orders, deliver services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us and recommend services that might be of interest to you. We also use this information to improve our website and platform, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

**How does www.kazeli.com protect my personal information?**

Kazeli takes significant steps to protect your personally identifiable information with secure servers. Any information you provide us is only maintained and accessed by Kazeli Holdings Ltd. In the event of a security breach beyond our control, Kazeli will notify any affected customers as soon as any such information becomes available to us.

**How do you handle Children Information?**

While www.kazeli.com focuses on providing business services, none of which directly targeted to children, we are committed to comply with applicable laws and requirements. Children without the consent of their parent or guardian should submit no personally identifiable information to the www.kazeli.com web site. www.kazeli.com will not knowingly collect from or use any personally identifiable information of children for any purpose, including disclosure to third parties.

**Will my data be transferred outside the EU?**

Because www.kazeli.com operates globally, we make information we collect available to our worldwide business units. For those of you visiting us from the European Economic Area, please note that www.kazeli.com may transfer your personally identifiable data outside the European Economic Area for use for any of the purposes described above. By using our web site and providing us with your personal data, you consent to such transfer of your personal data.

 **What if I still have questions regarding your Privacy Policy?**

We welcome your comments and questions regarding our Privacy Policy. Please direct all related comments/enquiries to: [privacy@kazeli.com](mailto:privacy@kazeli.com) and we will be happy to address them.
